

# JUN MING TEH (BRYAN)

# Final Year IT Undergraduate

# **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

A motivated and adaptable undergraduate student currently pursuing an Information Technology Degree BIT (Hons.) at Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia (UKM). I am ready to utilize my skills and passion to further the company's mission. Bringing forth a positive attitude, willing to learn and gain new experiences.

# CONTACT INFORMATION

Ш

+6011-10810285

Jun Ming Teh | LinkedIn

</>>

Jun Ming Teh | Portfolio

 $\bowtie$ 

ming58399@gmail.com

# REFERENCE

#### DR. TAN SIOK YEE (ESTHER)

Senior Lecturer Center For Artificial Intelligence Technology (CAIT) Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia (UKM) Phone: +6010-2188408

Email: <u>esther@ukm.edu.mv</u>

#### **EDUCATION**

# Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia (UKM) Bachelor of Information Technology with Honours, BIT (Hons.)

September 2019 – Expected to graduate in August 2023

Currently CGPA: 3.86

Related Courses: Mobile Programming, Web Programming, Modeling and System Simulation, Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP)

- Vice-Treasurer of Mobile Application Development (MAD) Club
- Student Developer of Google Developer Student Club (GDSC) UM
- Developed a First Aid and Healthcare Mobile Application: EmerCare

# Maktab Sultan Abu Bakar (English College, EC) Malaysian Higher School Certificate (STPM)

May 2017 - December 2017

- President of Malaysia School Youth Cadet Corps (KRS)
- Student Representative of Sixth Form Student Representative Council
- Commander of the Foot Drill Team

# **WORK EXPERIENCES**

# Full Stack Developer Ascend Com Sdn. Bhd.

August 2022 - Mar 2023 (8 months), Internship

Managed 4 projects during the internship

- 3 internal projects and 1 external project
- Handled front-end (Vue.is and Tailwind CSS) and back-end (Laravel)
- Utilized agile methodology and collaborated with Project Executive
- Coordinated with UI/UX Designer to upload assets to AWS S3
- Conducted testing using LambdaTest towards products
- Worked with colleagues using versioning tools (Git/GitHub)
- Deployed projects to staging/production using Laravel Vapor
- Independently developed an online ticketing web application
- Organized product launch event and served as receptionist

#### **Student Mentor**

# Faculty of Information Science and Technology (FTSM), UKM

November 2020 - Jun 2022 (I year 8 months), Seasonal

Mentored over 10 mentees in the field of

- Java Programming Language
- Object-oriented Programming (OOP)
- Graphical User Interface (GUI) and Data Structures

# **SKILLS**

- Java, XML, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP
- Android, Vue.js, Laravel, MySQL, NoSQL and Git
- Unity, Adobe XD, Adobe Photoshop and AutoCAD
- Microsoft Word, Excel and PowerPoint
- English, Malay and Chinese Language
- Leadership, Teamwork and Critical Thinking

# **HONORS AND AWARDS**

- Jabatan Perkhidmatan Awam (JPA) Scholar
- Dean's List Award for up to 7 semesters
- Excellent Mentor Award for up to 2 sessions